mobilism.me 2017-09-20

# Privacy policy | Mobilism

**Privacy Policy**  
Last modified: 11 March 2010

Mobilism recognizes that your privacy is important. This privacy policy applies to services provided by Mobilism on the domains and subdomains ending in .mobilism.org

If you have any questions relating to this privacy policy, feel free to [contact us](http://forum.mobilism.org/ppcw.php?mode=contact).

 **Information we collect**  
Most of the services Mobilism offer do not require you to register in order to access them, however some premium services may require you to register such as the [search engine](http://forum.mobilism.org/search.php).

  *  _Personal information:_ You have the ability to use Mobilism completely anonymously. No personal information is collected or held by Mobilism unless you choose to provide it to us, with the exception of your email address. No one from Mobilism will ever ask for your personal identifying information such as your name, social security number, address or phone number. If you have been asked for this information by someone posing as Mobilism, [contact us](http://forum.mobilism.org/ppcw.php?mode=contact) and let us know.
  *  _Cookies:_ When visiting Mobilism a small piece of information called a [cookie](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) is sent from our server and stored on your computer. The cookie set by Mobilism contains a small bit of information, such as your user id (which enables you to be logged in), and your last visit time. The cookies set by Mobilism only contain necessary information required for our service to work. When logging in you are offered the choice of a session cookie (which is removed when you close your browser) or a persistent cookie (by clicking the box labelled 'Log me on automatically each visit'). A persistent cookie will remain stored on your system until you log out, a year passes without visiting Mobilism again, or you click 'Delete all board cookies' located on the lower left of the index page.
  *  _Third-party cookies:_ Mobilism contains features from third party vendors, such as the wibiya toolbar and advertisements. These services are provided directly from the vendor's website and may also set cookies on your computer to enable you to use their features in a more effective manner. Mobilism is not responsible for the cookies third party vendors set. If you would like more information about the cookies that may be set by third party vendors, please read the privacy policy on their website.
  *  _Logging:_ Mobilism does _not_ keep access logs via our http server. However, forum logs are kept when certain actions are performed such as posting or donating WRZ$. These logs are kept for auditing purposes only and are on used by Mobilism to confirm actions are legitimate or perform actions such as banning. The logs we collect vary, but most contain only user id, action performed, and time of action.
  *  _Links and other sites:_ This privacy policy applies to Mobilism only. There may be external sites embedded (such as images) and external links supplied via Mobilism. These sites will contain their own privacy policies relating to the collection and use of data. Mobilism is not responsible for these external sites.

 **Information we disclose**  
No information is disclosed to any external organisations or vendors except automatically collected information (see third-party cookies above). No manually collected information will ever be disclosed without notifying you and obtaining your consent.

 **Your choices**  
At any time you may log out and continue to use the services of Mobilism anonymously. You may also update the information stored by Mobilism by clicking on 'User Control Panel' after logging in.

 **Data security**  
All data collected by Mobilism is stored securely in an encrypted format. No data is, or ever will be, transmitted on any insecure or portable formats such as USB keys or CD-ROMs. However, while all physical and technical safe-guards are taken to keep data secure, Mobilism is unable to guarantee a security systems breach will never happen. In the event of a security systems breach, Mobilism will attempt to notify you electronically advising you to take appropriate protective steps. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should [contact us](http://forum.mobilism.org/ppcw.php?mode=contact). All data transmitted to Mobilism is done so at your own risk.

 **Changes to this policy**  
This policy may be updated from time to time without notice. The effective date of the latest change will always be displayed on the top of this page as 'Last modified'. If any significant changes are made to this privacy policy, such as reducing your rights, we will post an announcement in the [announcements forum](http://forum.mobilism.org/viewforum.php?f=1).
